smartwebsearch.info 2016-03-23

# Privacy Policy | Smart Web Search

Welcome http://www.smartwebsearch.info/ operated by or for the SMART-WEB-SEARCH society. SMART-WEB-SEARCH takes respect your privacy seriously. Please please read the following to learn more about our site’s privacy policy and the ways in which we use your information before you place the use of the website.  
Purpose of this Website Privacy Policy

This privacy policy of the site covers the treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected when you are on the website and when you use the services of the website, as described in the Site Privacy Policy.  
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SMART-WEB-SEARCH owns or does not control, or to people that SMART-WEB-SEARCH employs or does not manage, including, without limitation, third party advertisers or sponsors to whom you provide information. SMART-WEB-SEARCH is not responsible for the policies or practices of respect for the privacy of other web sites you choose to link to from the website and encourages you to review the policies of respect for privacy these other websites so that you can understand how they collect, use and share information.

Collection and Use of Information  
SMART-WEB-SEARCH does not collect identifying personal information when you access the home page of the website and browsing the website.

Exchange and Information Sharing  
SMART-WEB-SEARCH may send personal identifying information about you to other companies or people when:  
we respond to subpoenas from, court orders or legal process;  
we believe it is necessary, as we have established freely, to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, emergency situations involving potential threats to security Physics of any person, violations of Terms of Use http://www.smartwebsearch.info/, or as the law requires otherwise.

Third party advertising  
Other companies that are presenting advertisements on some pages may set their cookies on your computer and access it. The use of their cookies by other companies is subject to their own site’s privacy policies, not this one.  
Security

We have implemented technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information against accidental loss, unauthorized access and use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and we can not guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to neutralize these measures or use your personal information for illicit purposes.

If you contact SMART-WEB-SEARCH email, you should note that the secrecy of Internet email is uncertain. By sending e-mail messages or sensitive or confidential information which are not encrypted you accept the risk of such uncertainty and possible lack of confidentiality over the Internet.

Changes in that site’s privacy policy.  
This policy may be changed if necessary. If we change the privacy policy of the site in any way, we will put an updated version on this page of the website. The fact of regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we will share them with others. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by broadcasting an ad well development on the site.
